{"data":[{"question":"He will flatly _________ that he is responsible for the accident.","a":"decline","b":"deny","c":"refuse","d":"reject","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Deny + that + Clause: to say that something is not true, or that you do not believe something ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"64","subcategorylv2":"7","type":"1"},{"question":"What did Peter do? \"He _________ asleep all morning.\"","a":"lay","b":"laid","c":"lain","d":"lying","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Simple past tense \n- Lie - Lay - lain","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"64","subcategorylv2":"7","type":"1"},{"question":"Will eighty dollars be enough? \"Another twenty ___\"","a":"will do","b":"will cover","c":"will fix","d":"will fine","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Do: used to say that something will be enough or be acceptable","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"64","subcategorylv2":"7","type":"1"},{"question":"They, having many children, want to ___ a servant.","a":"let","b":"hire","c":"rent","d":"lend","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Hire: to employ someone for a short time to do a particular job \n- Rent: to regularly pay money to live in a house or room that belongs to someone else, or to use something that belongs to someone else \n- Lend:to let someone borrow money or something that belongs to you for a short time \n- Let: to allow someone to do something ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"64","subcategorylv2":"7","type":"1"},{"question":"I couldn't afford to ___ a house like that.","a":"rent","b":"borrow","c":"spend","d":"use","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Rent: to regularly pay money to live in a house or room that belongs to someone else, or to use something that belongs to someone else \n- Borrow: to use something that belongs to someone else and that you must give back to them later \n- Spend: to use your money to pay for goods or services \n- Use: if you use a particular tool, method, service, ability etc, you do something with that tool, by means of that method etc, for a particular purpose","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"64","subcategorylv2":"7","type":"1"},{"question":"He always _________ his dictionary when he comes across a difficult word.","a":"consults","b":"opens","c":"looks","d":"seeks","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Consult: to look for information in a book, map, list etc","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"64","subcategorylv2":"7","type":"1"},{"question":"The president ___ a good income .","a":"pleases","b":"asks","c":"enjoys","d":"satisfies","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Enjoy something \n- Please with sth \n- Ask for sth \n- Satisfy sth ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"64","subcategorylv2":"7","type":"1"},{"question":"What has _________ of him?","a":"been","b":"become","c":"got","d":"done","answer":"2","explain":"\n- What became of ...?\/whatever will become of ...?: used to ask what has happened to someone or something, especially when you have not seen them for a long time, or what will happen to someone that you are worried about","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"64","subcategorylv2":"7","type":"1"},{"question":"A wooden building can easily ___ fire.","a":"reach","b":"spreads","c":"burn","d":"catch","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Catch fire: if something catches fire, it starts to burn accidentally","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"64","subcategorylv2":"7","type":"1"},{"question":"We can ___ seats for you only if you pay in advance.","a":"take","b":"reserve","c":"acquire","d":"cancel","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Reserve something for somebody\/something: to arrange for a place in a hotel, restaurant, plane etc to be kept for you to use at a particular time in the future","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"64","subcategorylv2":"7","type":"1"}]}